name: 'Irregular Verbs'
questions:
  -
    question: 'They $ in Brazil last week.'
    answers:
      - are
      - was
      - were
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'It $ to snow.'
    answers:
      - began
      - begun
      - begin
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'Iâ€™m sorry I $ the window.'
    answers:
      - broken
      - break
      - broke
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'We $ some food in the market.'
    answers:
      - buy
      - bout
      - bought
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'She $ speak Russian when she was four.'
    answers:
      - can
      - could
      - coud
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'They $ to class last week.'
    answers:
      - come
      - came
      - camed
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'I $ my homework in the evening.'
    answers:
      - done
      - made
      - did
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'We $ a lot of coffee.'
    answers:
      - drank
      - drunk
      - drink
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'He $ very fast because he was in a hurry.'
    answers:
      - drove
      - drives
      - driven
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'I $ a lot yesterday.'
    answers:
      - eat
      - ate
      - eaten
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'They $ an apartment downtown.'
    answers:
      - found
      - find
      - founded
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'We $ up early this morning.'
    answers:
      - get
      - gotten
      - got
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'I $ Anna a birthday present.'
    answers:
      - give
      - given
      - gave
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'They $ on vacation in July.'
    answers:
      - go
      - gone
      - went
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'I $ my old car for 15 years.'
    answers:
      - haved
      - had
      - have
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'We $ a noise during the night.'
    answers:
      - heard
      - heared
      - heard
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'I $ all the answers.'
    answers:
      - knew
      - know
      - known
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'The train $ the station at 8:00.'
    answers:
      - leaved
      - left
      - leaves
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'I $ my keys on the train.'
    answers:
      - lost
      - losed
      - lose
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'John $ dinner last night.'
    answers:
      - maked
      - maden
      - made
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'I $ a lot of people at the university.'
    answers:
      - meeted
      - met
      - meet
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'I $ by credit card in the restaurant.'
    answers:
      - payd
      - paid
      - payed
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'They $ a lot of books on vacation.'
    answers:
      - read
      - readed
      - readen
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'We $ our bikes in the park'
    answers:
      - rode
      - ridden
      - ride
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'I $ I was sorry.'
    answers:
      - said
      - sayd
      - sayed
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'I $ an old friend at the party.'
    answers:
      - seed
      - seen
      - saw
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'He $ a lot of emails.'
    answers:
      - send
      - sent
      - sented
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'They $ near the window.'
    answers:
      - sat
      - sit
      - satted
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'I $ for 4 hours last night.'
    answers:
      - sleep
      - slept
      - sleeped
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'We $ Chinese to the waiter.'
    answers:
      - spoke
      - speak
      - spoken
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'I $ every day when I was in Mexico.'
    answers:
      - swim
      - swimmen
      - swam
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'Jane $ good pictures of the house.'
    answers:
      - taken
      - tooken
      - took
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'I $ my children a story last night.'
    answers:
      - told
      - tell
      - said
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'We $ the music was terrible.'
    answers:
      - thought
      - thinked
      - think
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'I $ my new boots to the party.'
    answers:
      - wear
      - wore
      - worn
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'She $ a lot of emails this morning.'
    answers:
      - write
      - written
      - wrote
    correct: 3
